To all the authority for today's date and time, item two is the implication by Pastor of First Assembly of God,
President and for sale.
Thank you for being here tonight.
Thank you.
Let's pray.
It's a follow.
Thank you for your wonderful prayer for our lives and for your son Jesus Christ.
We ask for your wisdom on this being, this evening.
You direct every decision or just let your presence be here.
Thank you, Lord, for blessing our city, our businesses, our leaders, our city council.
We ask you to continue to direct us or bless our churches and for those that are in our beauty.
Thank you for your war that's hurtful, we just thank you for crowning us even with your presence.
Bless those that serve in our community, it's firemen of peacemen and those that are with their self and harm
way.
You just keep them in cover with your presence and protect it, especially the Lord of these days, which we
live, as we remember those in Texas and have lost a lot of the families that are suffering, we
are going to be a whole family and we just bless this nation again with your wonderful love
and Jesus name.
Amen.
Thank you.
I pledge allegiance to the body of the United States of America and to the Republic for which it's
saying, my nation, we're out, the individual, we live in our city in Texas for all.
Thank you.
Okay.
To recess the Council meeting for a moment and call it to order the.
Our students recess the MSJ meeting, called order the council meeting.
Would you mind going within our special guests while we.
Right quick.
Item number 2 is an announcement of November 7, 2017, Proclamation on her outstanding service to the
community.
And I believe Needles is going to bring in some special guests here in just a moment.
See who it is. So, Jim, what do you think that evening, O game?
That was something, right?
That's why you just kept swiping in a bottle and getting it next week.
Yep. What's that airplane here?
Yeah.
Why didn't I think it was a little bit down there, or...
About five hours?
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
Yeah, five and a half.
It's called, especially since I have game on Friday night,
and you keep back to it right up the list.
I guess you've been up a few like a night ride in stories, huh?
For how many years now?
40 years.
We have 40 years of cover, my answer.
Do you recognize anybody?
Should we say 40 of you here, Jim?
Well, good for you.
We've got something we like to present you.
We told you we had a surprise on the agenda.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm going to show you.
We have a population that's young lady.
They're off the lead.
You know what I was going to read?
Today of November 7, 2017 as Jim Ellis Day in the city of Miami, Ottawa County, Oklahoma.
Whereas mayor Rudy Schultz and the Miami City Council believes it is important to recognize citizens
who distinguish themselves by various means and who have made significant contributions in our community.
And whereas the Miami City Council believes that Jim Ellis is such individual where they are being recognized
for his significant contributions to this community and whereas Jim Ellis has been the sports editor of the Miami news record
since 1977 and covered sports for the Sequoia County Times from 1975 to 1977.
Miami native in 1971 graduate of Miami High School in 1973 graduate of Northeastern Oklahoma and in college in 1977 graduate
of Northeastern State University and whereas Jim Ellis was inducted into the Oklahoma 8th Ann High School football Hall of Fame in 2011.
A member of the Oklahoma Press Association, Porter Centric Club and a member of the organizing committee of the Oklahoma 8th Ann football coaches association all far game.
And whereas Jim Ellis was inducted to the Oklahoma Press Association Journalism Hall of Fame and whereas Jim Ellis continues to cover more than six local high schools,
plus any OAMM and assist with pace, design, photography and feature stories as well as news coverage.
Now therefore the it results that mayor Rudy Schultz and Miami City Council do hereby recognize the work of Jim Ellis and declared November 7, 2017 as Jim Ellis Day within the city of Miami.
In witness thereof, I appear on two set my hand and pause the seal of city of Miami, Oklahoma to be in fix on the 7th day of November in the year horrible or 2017.
It's been a long time, man, to get you here, too.
Oh!
Go down.
Hey, guys.
I really want to thank you for this honor, this blows me away.
You know, my name is home.
It's always been home, you know, as I say, once a word, always a word, but as my
twitter says, I bleed blue.
Those are both my and my high school and NEO.
So, hey, I really want to thank you for this, and you guys got me with you, that is crazy.
That is crazy.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you, nice to meet you.
Thank you, Melinda, and all our generous family for helping us sign up for the latest
thing to go now as in future.
Is he free to go?
Okay.
You really want to.
Do you guys work today?
Yeah.
And thank you.
Thank you.
Okay.
Well, Jim Mia's got a couple of things he wants to say.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Danny, we were a pretty shake to game.
We, we meet a lot to my am I?
And nobody does anything.
you know I'm trying. There's you can't be feel. I'm trying as much as I can. I know you do.
It'll be out Facebook Live. Thank you all again.
So what you got in the appropriate.
Okay, so we're now going to recess the council meeting.
Go back to the special utility authority meeting.
We are at I don't know which is public input and unscheduled personal priorities.
We're going to decide to jam that we're seeing to address the authority on any of the items.
Tom, you've got a couple of guests in the audience, from GRDA.
Would you just introduce them, please?
We're not asking you to get up and tell you about unless you want to.
But they just might have recognized you for being here. We'll appreciate it.
Well, guys, we're really appreciate you being here.
No one else will go to the council agenda.
I don't stand with you up any night. I'm six and seven for the consent agenda.
If there are no.
questions on Inter-Canter-Most Sure Approve?
Posted for that.
On the second.
Sir.
We'll call please.
Something.
I'd like to thank you.
Hi.
Forster.
We'll be with a show.
Hi.
Thank you.
I'm Ed Mett, discussion on Water and a sewer, a capital improvement plan.
All on John.
He's got some roll-up too.
In front of a person.
Yes, sir.
We brought some that we replaced in time.
I'm a community.
If you're in the North West, you'd be address-be-water, we've been pushing hydrants, so my
shoulders are sore.
You know.
Robert, did you get in the face today?
So...
By a constituent?
Oh, man.
I don't know.
What about the broken stem?
Oh, broken?
I was full, and I was full in New Orleans.
Okay.
I'm all on my arm.
I'm a bruise on one of my legs.
Yeah.
I thought we'd have dives.
So we're going to get started this session on the Water and a sewer capital improvement plan.
So that could maybe be met.
And the last thing we left on is the MSU-A access to it, that's in the alternate funding
opportunities, and also to provide better plan and better kind of an estimated cost and
immediate needs for the plan.
So we went there and did that.
First off, we looked at different ways for funding.
So we looked at free money.
So everybody likes free money.
So we've got the Toyota BRB.
We checked with them on the drinking water side.
So DWS are at, they have free money for regionalization.
So if we want to take on another community's water, I'm going to have the interest in, or if
one's a system is taken over by other systems.
So for example, I'd have some of the Mesa cities.
They might take over a rural water industry.
If it's important for them if they're expanding that direction, something that goes right
now we don't have that.
But they do not have any free money to replace existing lines in the community.
Okay?
So we built them out.
Then we went on the suicide, which is the Clean Water State for Quality and Fund.
So you also referred to a CWSRF.
You have to meet the state of reliability, which we did meet that, but we did not meet the population.
So you had to be 3300 people or less to meet that.
So obviously we don't fit that.
The second thing the afternoon money for was for green projects.
None of our projects meet that.
So green projects would be for everyone at the pervious pavement down in certain areas for
one of the rain and the water to go in there for storm water runoff.
Different things like that, but I'm always to recycle water, but none of our plans we talked
to other plans meant that it's re-warned.
So can I just interject there and ask about in front of the colonel?
Is that not something that you mentioned as a possibility?
It is a possibility we could, you still have to have the water to go somewhere, even if it
goes into a permeable pavement, we still have to send it somewhere else.
Okay.
And right now down the stream is not off.
The streams are only option.
We just need to work on how we did that down.
The intensity.
Okay.
Real quick.
What about with the future splash pad with the water that's not going to be recycled?
Does that qualify for anything that's coming off and you're going to be runoff from the splash pad?
Does that?
Nothing.
I'm not 100% on that one there.
Because a lot of water is going to be used and it's just going to go down just away.
All of this.
It sounded like it was a blow through system.
It was out a lot of recycled.
Right.
It has the treatment requirements for recaptured, rather than...
The next thing we look down is the Indian Health Services Funding.
So previous people have worked with them here at the city, so we checked in and then began to see if they would have any ways to help us.
We talked to them about some different projects and we are their population criteria to 10,000 or less.
So we were over that.
The only way to help us is if there was any additional Indian homes that were built that would like to connect to the system and then they would help us with that.
But as far as the projects that we had, they could not help us.
The last one we looked to and we talked to was the U.S.P.A.
So the U.S. Department of Agriculture and World Development.
So we reached out to them on the different programs that have a lot of different programs that we met with them.
They also have the same requirement of the population of 10,000 or less.
So we could not meet that for that.
Then we talked to you over and we would be about a lot of them.
So they have different loan programs that they offer.
So the first loan program is the FAP loans.
So this is, they go out and get a bomb for three or four different cities to get a lower interest rate.
And then in turn, they make the loan to you for them not because you want it.
With that, you don't have to do that.
If I don't want to stay with Spain again, different, and then American Island is still.
But they, that you are required to pay interest as soon as you get the loan.
And some of the other programs we're going to talk about here in a minute.
You don't start interest in carrying until you actually spend the money.
Okay?
So, I mean, FAP works for both water and sewer projects.
So there is funding available.
It's just whether or not we want to pursue that.
Yes, there is.
So this is the last time they close to big deals in June.
This is just kind of showing you the years and the places that borrow the money in the per cent.
I'm sorry.
I'll go back to that slide.
So the term affected the rate.
Otherwise, the rate was the same.
That you should have been dependent on the term.
Okay.
Thank you.
And so the benefits is that I take you bombs.
So you have never reserved it.
If you get covered just 1.4 per.
And then there's no available environment.
Switch some of the other programs around.
Talk about a minute, dude.
Call for that.
So the second program they talked about with us was the Clean Water State Revolving
From.
So this is for wastewater projects, which I know the need to think,
think, worry, think of everything, whatever.
It's actually wastewater.
So you can also do stormwater projects with this money.
So the interest rates are significantly discounted thanks to the EPA backing on this program and it does not require
Interesting to you actually spend the money. So if we borrow nine if we borrow two before and half me a dollar for a share of projects
So they would hold that money for us until we actually spent that money down
So each project we did they would we would not be paying interest on until we actually spent that money on the project
So that's kind of an extent to that program. It does require environmental review
Which they said takes 45 days and 60 days and they explained what he just which around here
It wasn't that different American iron steel and if this was sustainability plan
So invasive all stuff that they have people that help you with
You're saying American iron steel. You're talking about the materials. Yes, I guess all products on the
We'll have a certificate basically the days of American steel similar to our project if they had out several years ago
So the requirements that you have behavior requires an environmental review
You have the day of the state and like we talked about in our ground steel and the fiscal sustainability plan
So this is not a project that we would do in house you can do
Probably see that and also in house say so there's Davis bacon apply for doing it in house
I don't know why it would you know, paying whatever or probably way please
I've been on tip-weaning this value for example
But it's dead for objects that have to follow those
Then the second thing is the drinking water state revolving from which is DWS RF
It's for water-related projects are a drinking water
It's similar to the CWS RF but the discounts a little bit less so it's 30% to the 40
And they have similar but not identically every department and it's also a communist with deep deep so you will continue to find projects
This is the breakdown of recent projects that they've done in the interest rate
So you can see this is wow nice right
Okay, and they said you know if you wanted to do if you want to borrow money for 15 years, but pay it back
Do two years of construction then pay it back for the 13 and I have you could actually get a little interest rate than the 15 years
So
So when it's said in six-month increments, I'd basically draw every six months
No, you give all of my money for every so you want to do 15 and a half years or
The terms yes, the term so next
We're about the capital plan for the water and so this is the second thing that MSU and board ask is to have a more defined plan
So
And we're also going to talk about you the bump funny that will then
present it with Dan Jackson and
Also when after this let's get changed if there was economic development things that came along the view and have to prioritize
Project differently and then also besides this we will also continue to replace
We're seeing five and ten blocks of water line in the year.
And what's our morning year that we had four years ago, five years of those purchase.
Then this year we've got nine subparallel sharing, so.
And is that just out of operating problems?
That just kind of...
It's a very good work we've been doing in addition to major projects.
Yes, sir.
So we've been working over the Northwest in our thighs.
Olsen's engineering central.
So we're going to start working on some of those lines in those neighborhoods.
Off those central stuff.
So here's our water capital plan.
It's including your packet.
This is best for you to get it to share with on the PowerPoint.
Kind of something interesting.
We brought something interesting.
Water line.
So this is the two-inch water line that we removed.
And if you see all of a sudden excitement.
This is like what a stirred up whenever we flush the hydrants in.
So this is...
Guess who made the original one?
About 100?
I would say goes to 100.
Here's the one in service.
It's like everybody likes to look to it.
There it is.
It's about half.
It's a three-quarter school.
So that would be actually coming from a main here house.
And then we have this morning.
First of all, it probably should've recently did.
I don't know what we've ordered any water line.
Which is one of some of it's kind of came out.
Because we had to beat it out to do it to come loose.
And it has some interesting pictures up here.
If anybody would like to see that.
And those are all cash done.
Yes.
So one thing to forward move.
That total cost of kind of all of these is high.
It's not half of the bond.
And the reason behind that is if it crisis come in better.
You don't have to have the next knife on the list.
So that it gets moved on.
We're only going to spend what we can't spend.
But if we get good bit, crisis, we want to keep it moving forward.
So on the board, all of these tables, basically, that table again.
So these items that are highlighted.
These are on the priority list.
All the other dark finds.
That's the rest of the list.
So don't think that once we get through the first more team or finish.
There's a lot more work to do.
And these are just immediate priorities.
All lines, things that haven't been replaced.
So basically, anything that was cast is on this list.
And are these all point and bigger?
Or are they?
They're everything.
I mean, they're up to 14.
So.
But they're all major feeder lines.
I guess we'll be a way to say it.
So the first one on our list is central.
If you guys remember, we passed the two.
we passed the record, you had also an engineer central for a few blocks, so I mean, that
is a main grid there.
And the second one is, this is our sewer capital plan, so for the first phase we kind
of do it along the river, you can see on that map, is there a main area or a main area?
So the ones we picked here, basically, lower line areas, places where infiltration is a
little more likely to get back into the line, so low spot along the river, another low spot
there in northeastern, turn this over, turn this over, I think that will help everybody
for you, little bit easier.
Thank you.
And if people have ever been out to the train bridge where we have the sewer line that goes
across the train, all the train bridge, so that's one of them that we're going to replace.
So again, the tower, the long stretch, you're running along the river, you're proposing
replacing that sewer.
So how does that mesh with our 20-year plan for the community and growth and letting some
spaces return to their natural way, if you will?
Right now, that's where the sewer goes, so even if that becomes more of a natural area, you're
still going to have a sewer line there, because the entire city, the residential density there
has a matter, so there's a line going as well, everything's going.
Yeah, this all feeds over to the river, and then follows the river down to the pump station
and then comes back to the plant.
So, really feed, come to the situation.
But in those lines, so your flood study coming up, one of the things to look at is waterproofing
those mammals, so that when the river does get about them to make sure that you don't have
the Neo-Show River coming into your sewer system.
And that's the influx of infiltration.
Right, big issue.
Yes, so the point for all of these is the slipwinding similar to what we just finished out
at the Neo.
Some of them in this priority are only animal work, trying to get those rims up above flood
point elevation, so that they quit sucking in and storm water.
And then our one forced main project to get your forced main off of that old threshold.
Okay.
And here's the map that's on us.
And this is the dead forecast of that.
The injects a particular employee study.
So, if you notice that nine million for the first phase and then six and six and four.
And the numbers from the two choices.
are you presenting earlier or about 10 and a half million, is that right?
Yes, so the difference is coming from just operating.
We don't know actually.
The difference will come down.
We will hit nine.
You want to stop.
But if the big price has come in.
That would have been the budget.
We want.
You got to have me or the projects.
Yeah.
That's the estimated cost.
We're going to bond that nine.
And if we get, if we can do all that, we will.
We'll start working on, you know, probably one fruit.
Yes.
We get done with probably nine of we have an, the Nancy, probably ten.
A lot of priority ten, we'll start working on.
Now, I think one thing that we're talking about, and as I've been very important to talk about in my note,
is with the safe fund.
There's some very real opportunities with that.
Instead of borrowing the large amount of money at first.
Starting to work with the state on loans for things like many.
Priorities one and two are getting those in class.
We would need to be paying interest on those until actually we pulled the money.
So in reality, instead of having, but in was anticipated for our rates.
I'd be able to stretch that out.
And I don't have our rates to look as quickly.
It's highly possible.
Maybe for the first two projects or so.
It might be a year before we look at any kind of rating.
So that's what I really like to start exploring.
The state is that even though we wouldn't have to be paying day to stay in.
Research definitely not that much of a difference.
But if we don't actually start paying interest on that, then we can start working with them.
Figure out where our rates are.
And probably they have a much longer rating crisis than what he was showing this last night.
And try to try to develop a plan like that.
But there's this to be clear on the financing mechanism.
There's still bonding that's done for the state.
It would be staged differently.
Because for example, our electric projects that we want to.
That's the traditional office.
So once we're ready on that, we're already working on.
The, is it the, because the initial substation is going to be first.
That's about four million other projects.
And probably right after the first one year with your approval on the market.
You do that on the balance bondage.
And then we'll have our rates are already designed.
We'll go to effective April to be able to pay off that bondage.
Here we have it done.
And since we have a different mechanism to that.
We might, you know, try to try to get loans for projects.
One, two, three depending on how long those will pay.
Part of the money for that through the bondage process.
And then by the time we get four by six, do it again.
And then have much smaller papers.
on increases in the rate.
And do remember, we didn't have 5% rate of increases
built into more water as so we're 3, 2019.
So I think our goal here is that we'll do these projects
and it's the same amount of time,
but not have as a big impact on our customers.
So a comment and then a couple of questions.
Number one, I appreciate your thoroughness.
The two guys went to this with,
especially looking for the free money first.
But then I talked just very casually and formally
over the last year about debt opportunities.
And it's clearly, you guys really went out
and researched it and I probably had an opportunity
to learn a lot about how some of this stuff works.
Secondly, I bring not the free money,
but the next group of money is one of those required
of one point forward in debt coverage ratio.
And is that one of what we're proposing using?
Yes, OK.
And is that ratio only with respect to our water debt
or is that the city's overall debt?
And it's a good idea.
I think the bonds we have right now are best of it.
I think one point forward, one point five ratio.
And so that we've done some projections
on what the electric bonding is going to do to that ratio.
Bands, the race that we have,
the race that we've already approved,
that accurate in that ratio to the non-linear bondage.
So we already have that only before we start together.
We have not done that yet for water,
and it's super expensive.
We need to work with Dan on depending on our projects.
And if we use that source of funding,
that we have to kind of restructure how it will be looking at that.
So we've got some going to do it on that.
But the nice thing about that is that how will we work on it?
The rating increases will be less than the change
over the project before the SQF9ment bondage.
So any changes will make the people
that the rating increases will be less non-linear.
But we start out to meet that ratio.
This is going to make sure we're looking down the road
at the electric bonding.
This is what the enters in it.
Just what our current rates are,
plus if we would put that.
But obviously those would change with the fixing out.
So I do want to, I do want to put that to me.
I think that would be talking about the coverage.
Dan's numbers have impacted that.
I'm looking at children because what Jill knows about you
suddenly said, we do those bond issues.
Our ability to be able to have that coverage
to be able to pull up money from initially
in general funds is going to be restricted.
So that's going to reason why we keep talking about that restriction
is that we have to keep that coverage.
And we'll have a very similar situation.
We'll start in the water soon.
I'm not sure you'd have any pictures from our other close-end issues show in the importance of this morning, but this is first and seed, and that's full blast.
So that's what it should be like, that's a new water main we did.
I'm here recently, we did an announcement this in the period of morning units.
And so why did the difference in the two?
That's a brand new water line versus you know what it's been there 80 to over a year.
And the show, the difference in flow is because it's clogged up.
Yes, there it does.
I have all the sediments.
Thank you, sorry, sorry.
There's one more fourth in E.
I'm right there, I was glad we didn't get call because we didn't think it was going to happen.
So probably it is.
So that's what it should be like.
Right.
This is a sewer that's just kind of showing you what they've been doing.
Before we could away from the hyper festival,
I'm going to say one thing, looking at Robert appears there.
Our, you know, for the record, our ISO record.
About 40% of our ISO record is dependent on our water source.
And you can see what the fire hydrants with that flow coming out.
Why do we have that situation?
That's why I know some people are sending the virus to the water.
And all that, that's why you do the flush.
It's not only the clean out flow lines, but also to have an idea of what your fire flow is on your lines.
And then prioritize an important.
So this is going to have a huge effect.
You know, being in the youth projects we're dealing.
We'll also have a few people's insurance.
Right.
Shouldn't agree with us, it shouldn't.
It shouldn't.
It's really stupid.
That's why the fire department is still involved with the highly flushes.
Because it relates to our ability to fight fibers.
And this is the answer line.
If you guys are in a very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very bad.
So we're going to have that sort of line.
So this is what it was before.
I'm going to get a picture after, but there are camera actually broken down.
So we haven't got the after picture yet from then.
But you can see that's a whole clay made.
And you see ups kind of starting to collapse in the cracks and then the roots coming in there.
So when they come in, it's the line that you know, they keep it for the, they cut all the roots out.
And then they slip on it for the roots can't penetrate.
So whenever they, no areas for the penetrating, no areas for water coming.
Yeah.
How much capacity do you lose some slip on?
No.
Honestly, you gain in some cases because the,
You're cleaning them out.
Well, you're cleaning them out.
But the smoothness of the liner is actually better than clay.
So in some cases, you actually improve capacity depending on kind of how long it's gotten.
You can see this has gotten just a little bit smashed.
So it's still roughly circular.
But in some cases, you won't lose just below.
Or are all the new materials, PBC?
Yes.
Schedule 40, or 80, or...
A lot of you are going to be probably H-D-P-E.
Okay.
A fusion joint, some kind of polypite.
So the CDC is in a lot of it.
They seem happy with it.
They've already got all the tools where they can...
Do you see the work with it?
So it seems you're going to stick with one material.
Yeah, about a hundred year long student.
Yeah.
So the CDC's similar to...
I mean, you're talking about it in your service live.
So...
Okay.
So this is the...
They'll be sure of us through a main, so the customer was having issues on their sewer.
We go out, we go out, and we can...
We can...
Just for the record that is docked there.
Yes, they're docked.
I'm talking in the grease.
They're...
They're all...
Yeah.
Which you can see.
Way down there.
So this is the service staff at the top.
And wait back there.
That is the joint of another pipe that's actually all right.
So almost a third of the pipe.
So...
That happens a lot in the clay.
I'm here's another one.
I'm worth the place.
This broken part.
So you can see the dirt actually there.
So...
And these sewer lines, no one would run.
The majority of these were they understreets.
They...
Sidewalls.
Under some streaks.
And that's what we have.
Yeah.
That guy like Chris.
I've most of you are actually running the alleys.
So what's your name?
Well, just cross your streaks.
What's your run into the soul of erosion in alleys and the breakdown there?
There's...
Well get a call that there's a sinkhole there.
Back there.
We'll go out and see if they...
So...
I think so that's...
That's the end.
So in the prioritizing of these...
Is it in...
Correlation with the...
Streaks projects that we are doing as well.
Well, or some of that will not have a lot of lander street and they go dig it up.
We're going to grab it all of our armor mains on the side of the street so we're not to go back.
That's what we're talking about with less than, is one of the reasons you can come along on the pavement.
Less than or so long is if the sewer water wants it in such a bad shape, you can get a repaid, you can probably be tearing it up again.
So now that we've got the project going to replace the water sewer, once that's done,
we'll be able to replace it and that must be wrong.
So some of them do correlate like on the water side, that is a street project as well.
So central is a perfect example to trap out is one of them.
You should be northeast is also in that list.
So those are all streets that were in street land.
A lot of them though are mainly looking at the house safe visor system.
If one of these goes down, what does that do in the rest of the system?
So one.
line is actually about on the 69-A, where your well is putting a tank out there, so that
that could be a stand-alone system, and there is also another line that's later on in
the priority list, and after we get the tank installed to connect another line back into that,
to feed down the C-Lo and its underneath turn-by. So they all kind of have a list, so once we
get the tank in place and we get that secondary connection, then we can go to the operations
center and start redoing pipe and pipe, because you have a secondary water source in case
something happens at the operations center and takes that off the line for us. So you can bring it
online and then go work on the other. So Chris has worked great with us, making sure that we need
to do this first and then this, and that way we can take these things offline, like you're all in
it doesn't hurt us. Another question? So next steps, it says up there.
Let me check with you. So next steps is, yeah, talking funding, going back,
well then, seeing what great impacts that has, if we go with your deferring interest payments.
Before we're going to, so at then, you know, we already have one major project I think we need to
here, we'll need to start mining on the other side. So the next time this will be back, before the
council will be January problem. At least. And I think we'll be lucky, Chris Jamford. So that's what I was saying
earlier is that if we, especially if we used to stay funding, you know, it's time to get the funding
approved, be being generic and all of that. Probably because of the year before that, actually,
getting some things going. This is, it takes that amount off. And that's why I'm saying that people
are going to be slowing down, and it can tolerate increases of water and sewer, other than the ones that
are already on the road, it's significant. And probably doing a much smaller increment, that's what we're
doing, that's what we're looking for, we're going to want large quantities. But remember, if you'd like to
project it's too, it would be the name of the substations, but four million years ago. So there
here's all the app, and that long issue is in the system. Okay. Questions? All right, great job, guys.
Thank you. Yeah, thank you. A little final thing for anybody watching the newspaper and all that,
and this is, it won't get any better. So, kind of this is something we actually had to do with any of
the markets themselves. Okay. Thank you, guys.
Thanks.
And out of nine, there's new business and new business in the staff reports, so if I did it for available.
11 is trusty and easy announcements in the announcement to anyone. I don't promise the German, you have much to join the SUAV.